serpfox.com 2012-05-25

# Serpfox - Privacy Policy

Brown Shoe Limited operates several websites including Serpfox.com. It is Brown Shoe Limited�s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Brown Shoe Limited collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Brown Shoe Limited�s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Brown Shoe Limited�s visitors use its website. From time to time, Brown Shoe Limited may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Brown Shoe Limited�s websites choose to interact with Brown Shoe Limited in ways that require Brown Shoe Limited to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Brown Shoe Limited gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, Brown Shoe Limited collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor�s interaction with Brown Shoe Limited. Brown Shoe Limited does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Brown Shoe Limited discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Brown Shoe Limited�s behalf or to provide services available at Brown Shoe Limited�s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Brown Shoe Limited�s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Brown Shoe Limited will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Brown Shoe Limited discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Brown Shoe Limited believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Brown Shoe Limited, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Brown Shoe Limited website and have supplied your email address, Brown Shoe Limited may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what�s going on with Brown Shoe Limited and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Brown Shoe Limited takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor�s computer, and that the visitor�s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Brown Shoe Limited uses cookies to help Brown Shoe Limited identify and track visitors, their usage of Brown Shoe Limited website, and their website access preferences. Brown Shoe Limited visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Brown Shoe Limited�s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Brown Shoe Limited�s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Brown Shoe Limited and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Brown Shoe Limited may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Brown Shoe Limited�s sole discretion. Brown Shoe Limited encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
